Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Music. Festivals (4)
    - Palm Beach Festival (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Paris Exposition (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Ravinia (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Royal Irish Academy of Music (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Salzburg (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Music Festivals (5)
    - Salzburg (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Serate Musicali Foundation Itd (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Spoleto (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Tanglewood (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Tanglewood (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Third Strict Music School Settlement (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - University of Michigan Music Society (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Festivals - Opera, General (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Concert Halls (1)
    - Concert Halls - general information (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Opera House - general information (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Opera Houses - Prints (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Academy of Music (New York) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Ambassador Auditorium (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - The Athenaeum (New York) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Arts Center (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Auditorium Theatre (Chicago) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Boston Music Hall (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Boston Opera House (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Boston Symphony Hall (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Bristol Opera House (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Carnegie Hall (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Concert Halls (2)
    - Central City Opera House (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Central College Regional Arts Center (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Centre Lyrigue de Wallouie (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Civic Opera (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Orchestra Hall (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Civic Center, Syracuse, N. Y. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Clowes Memorial Hall (Butter University) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Constitution Hall (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Covent Garden (Royal Opera House) (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Die Deutsche Staatsoper, Berlin (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - French Opera House (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Goodspeed Opera House (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Gray's Armory (Cleveland) (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Graz Operahouse (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Harlem Opera House (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Kennedy Center (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - La Scala (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Concert Halls (3)
    - Lincoln Center (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Opera House (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Boston Arts Center (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Monte - Carlo (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Mozarteum Argentino (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Concert Halls (4)
    - National Theatre for the Bavarian Opera-Music (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - New York City Center (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Odessa Opera House (U.S.S.R.) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Opera de Paris (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Opera Royal, Versailles (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Palace of Fine Arts (Mexico) (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Pavillion - L. A. Music Center (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia Academy of Music (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Philharmonic Hall (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Piper's Opera House (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Resdenztheaters, Munich (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller Center (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Rome Opera House (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Royal Albert Hall (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Shrine Mosque - Atlanta (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Springer Opera House (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Steinway Hall (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Sydney Opera House (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Tabor Opera House (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Teatro Colon (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Teatro Regio - Parma (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Teatro San Carlo (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Tenn. Performing Arts Center (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Theater An Der Wien (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Town Hall (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Troy Music Hall (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Verona Arena (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Vienna Opera House (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - War Memorial Auditorium (Boston) (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Warsaw Opera House (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - MET Tours (I)
    - Tour - General (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Music MET On Tour (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Tour Itineraries and Seat Assignments - Francis Robinson (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - MET Tours (2)
    - Atlanta (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Baltimore (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Birmingham (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Bloomington, Indiana (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - MET Tours (3)
    - Boston (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Boston (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Chattanooga (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Chicago (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - MET Tours (4)
    - Dallas (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Dallas (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Denver (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Des Moines (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Detroit (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Detroit (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - MET Tours (5)
    - Houston (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Japan (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Memphis (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Memphis (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Miami (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - MET Tours (6)
    - Minneapolis (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Minneapolis (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Montreal (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - New Haven (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - New Orleans (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Newark (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Nawport (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Oklahowa City (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Paris (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Philadelphia (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Rochester, NY (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - St. Louis (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Toronto (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Washington (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Singers (1)
    - Singers - general information (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Singers - Alphabetical (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Albanese, Licia (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Alda, Frances (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Elsa, Alsen (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Althouse, Paul (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Marian (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Anthony, Charles (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Baccaloni, Salvatore (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Bampton, Rose (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Baskerville, Nancy (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Bastianini, Ettore (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Belleri, Marguerite (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Bergonzi, Carlo (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Bjorling, Jussi (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Bledsoe, Jules (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Bonelli, Richard (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Bori, Lucrezia (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Brownlee, John (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Borkh, Inge (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Singers (2)
    - Callas, Maria, 1952 - 1956 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Callas, Maria, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Callas, Maria, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Callas, Maria, 1958 - 1959 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Callas, Maria, 1960 - 1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Callas, Maria, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Singers (3)
    - Callas, Maria undated programs (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Calve, Emma (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Carlton, Jean (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Carreras, Jose (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Carter, John (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Cehanovsky, George (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Chaliapin, Feodor (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Chapman, Frank (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Cigna, Gina (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Colt, Ethel (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Conner, Nadine (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Cordon, Norman (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Corelli, Franco (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Costa, Mary (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Crooks, Richard (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Singers (4)
    - Danco, Suzanne (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Darwin, Glenn (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Agnes (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Giuseppe de Luca (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Edith de Lys (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Alessio de Paolis (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Edouard de Reszke (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Jean de Reszke (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Mario del Monaco (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Giuseppe del Puente (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Denise, Givseppe (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Diaz, Justin() (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Dirman, Rose (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Juan de Curro (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Doe, Doris (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Domingo, Placido (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Eames, Emma (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Eddy, Nelson (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Edelmann, Otto (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Evans, Wilbur (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Farrar, Geraldine (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Farrell, Eileen (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Flagstad, Kisten (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Fredricks, Richard (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Fremstad, Olive (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - French, Norma (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Gadski, Johamma (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Galli-Curci, Amelite (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Garden, Mary (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Garris, John (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Gauthier, Eva (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Giannini, Dusolina (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Gigli, Beniamino (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Greer, Frances (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Guarrera, Frank (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Guthrie, Woody (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Singers (5)
    - Hagegard, Hakan (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Hayes, Roland (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Hempel, Frieda (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Hidalgo, Elviva de (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Hines, Jerome (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Homer, Louis (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Horne, Marilyn (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Jachmann-Wagner, Johanna (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Jagel, Frederick (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Jenkins, Florence Foster (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Jepson, Hellen (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Jeritza, Maria (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Journet (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Kiepura, Jan (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Kipnis, Alexander (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Kirsten, Dorothy (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Kocova, Mla (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Kurenko, Maria (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Lanza, Mario (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Lauri-Volpi, Giacomo (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Lawrence, Marjorie (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Lazzari, Carolina (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Lehmann, Lotte (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Lenya, Lotte (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Lewis, Richard (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Lind, Jenny (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - List, Emaruel (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Livingston, William (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - McCormack, John (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - McCormic, Mary (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Macpherson, Joseph (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - McCracken, James (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - MacNeil, Cornell (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Macurdy, John (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Maison, Rene (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Malone, Mary Cornelia (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Martinelli, Giovanni (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Martini, Nino (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Marvenga, use (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Mason, Edith (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Matzenauer, Margaret (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Maynor, Dorothy (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Singers (6)
    - Meisle, Kathryn (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Melba, Nellie (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Melchoir, Lauritz (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Meller, Raguel (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Melton, James (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Merrill, Robert (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Milanov, Zinka (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Milnes, Sherrill (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Minnelli, Liza (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Moffo, Anna (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Moore, Grace (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Morgana, Nina (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Morris, James (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Munsel, Patrice (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Nilsson, Birgit (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Nordica, Lillian (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Novoa, Salvador (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Novotna, Jarmila (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Magda, Olivero (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Singers (7)
    - Pagliughi, Lina (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Patti, Adelina (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Pauly, Rose (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Pavarotti, Luciano (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Pears, Peter (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Pease, James (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Peerce, Jan (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Petina, Irra (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Pinza, Ezio (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Gianni, Poggi (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Pons, Lily (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Ponselle, Carmela (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Ponselle, Rosa (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Price, Henry (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Price, Leontyne (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Singers (8)
    - Raith, John (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Rethberg, Elizabeth (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Rhodes, Jane (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Robeson, Paul (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Robeson, Paul (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Gail (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Rothier, Leon (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Ruffo, Titta (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Rysanck, Leonie (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Sammarco, Mario (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Sayao, Bidn (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Scheff, Fritzi (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Schipa, Tito (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Schorr, Friedrich (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Schwarz, Joseph (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Schwarzkopf, Elizabeth (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Scotti, Antonio (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Scotto, Renata (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Seemungal, Rupert P. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Shirley, George (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Sembrich, Marcella (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Siepi, Cesare (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Silia, Anja (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Sills, Beverly (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Singher, Martial (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Soederstroem, Elizabeth (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Spoto, Franco (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Singers (9)
    - Steber, Eleanor (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Rise (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Stoska, Polyna (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Stracciari, Riccardo (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Stratas, Teresa (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Strepponi, Givseppina (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Streisand, Barbra (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Stroeva, Dora (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Sutherland, Joan (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Swarthout, Gladys (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Tamagno, Francesco (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Tauber, Richard (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Tebaldi, Renata (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Terris, Norma (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Teyte, Maggie (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Thebom, Blanche (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Jess (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, John Charles (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Todd, Diane (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Tourel, Jennie (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Trapp Family Singers (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Tranbel, Hellen (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Truman, Margaret (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Tucci, Gabriella (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Tucker, Richard (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Tucker, Sophie (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Valentino, Francesco (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Valletti, Cesare (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Van Gordon, Cyrena (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Van Rooy, Anton (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Varnay, Astrid (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Viafora, Gina Aaparelli (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Vickers, Jon (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Von Stade, Frederica (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Warren, Leonard (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Waters, Ethel (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Weede, Robert (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - White, Robert (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Yergin, Sonja (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Singers - Groups (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Opera Companies (A - Con)
    - Abbott, Emma. The E. A. Grand English Opera Company (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Aborn English Grand Opera (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - American National Opera (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - American Opera Society (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Augusta Opera Association (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Bayerische Staatsoper (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Berlin City Opera (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Berlin State Opera (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Bolshoi Opera (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Boston English Opera (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Boston Lyric Company (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Boston Company (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Boston Opera Group (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Booklyn Opera Company (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Canadian Opera Co. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Castle Square Opera (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Central City Opera House (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Chautaugua Opera Association (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Opera (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Cincinnati Summer Opera (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut Opera (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Opera Companies (Coy - F)
    - Covent Garden (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Covent Garden (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Dallas Civic Opera (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Damrusch Opera Company (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Detroit Grand Opera Association (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - D'Oyly Carte Opera (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - English Opera Group (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Friends of French Opera (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Opera Companies (Ge - Lo)
    - German Grand Opera (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Goldovsky Opera Institute (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Goodspeed Opera House (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Gotham Light Opera (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Gran Teatro Del Licco (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Hamburg State Opera (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Hebrew National Opera (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Her Majesty's Opera (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Hinrick's Grand Opera (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Hinrich's New American Opera (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Houston Grand Opera (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Indian University Opera (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Juilliard American Opera Center (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Komische Opera (East Berlin) (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Kungsholm Miniature Grand Opera Theater (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - La Scala (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Lemonade Opera (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Light Opera of Manhattan (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Long Island Opera Co. (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Los Angeles Grand Opera (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Los Angeles Light Opera (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Opera Companies (Ly - Ne)
    - Lyric Opera of Chicago (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Mailander Scala (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Manhattan Grand Opera (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Marie Tavary Grand Opera (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Michigan Opera Company (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Opera Company (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Moscow Art Theatre Musical Studio (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - NBC Opera Theatre (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - National Grand Opera (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Net Opera Theater (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - New Imperial Opera (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - New Opera Company (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - New Orleans Opera (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - New York City Opera (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Opera Companies (Ni - 0)
    - Nine O'Clock Opera (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Opera Company of Jacksonville (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Opera Company of Philadelphia (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Opera D'Alaer (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Oprea de Monte-Carlo (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - L'Opera de Paris (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - L'Opera de Paris (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Opera Guild of Greater Miami (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Opera International (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Opera Nacional de Mexico (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Opera of the International Theatre (Prague) (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Opera Orchestra of New York (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Opera Studio (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Opera Theater, Inc. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Opera Theatre of New Jersey (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Opera Theatre of Syracuse (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Oratorio Society of New York (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Opera Companies (P - San)
    - Philadelphia - Chicago Opera (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia - La Scala (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Project Opera of Massachusetts (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Richmond Opera (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Rome Opera (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Royal Opera - Stockholm (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis Opera (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Salzburg Opera Guild (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - San Carlo Opera (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - San Diego Opera (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Civil Light Opera (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco Opera (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco Opera (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Opera Companies (San - W)
    - Santa Fe Opera (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Scotti Grand Opera (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Scottish opera Theatre Royal (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Seattle Opera (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Stadtische Buhnen (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Teatro Colon (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Teatro Comunale (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Teatro Dell 'Opera (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Teatro Di Corte (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Teatro Di San Carlo (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Teatro Massimo Bellini (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Teatro Massimo Palermo (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Theatre national De L'Opera Comique (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Washington Opera (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Wiener Staatsoper (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Operas (A - B)
    - Operas - general information (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Adriana Lecouvreur (Francesco Ciliea) (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - L'Africaine (Giacomo Mcyerbear) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Die Agyptische Helena (Richard Strauss) (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Aida (Verdi) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Alceste (Christoptre Willibald von Gluck) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - L'Amorc dei tre Re (Italo Montemezzi) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Andrea Chenier (Umberto Giordano) (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Aniara (Karl-Birger Blomdahl) (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Antony and Cleoputra (Samuel Barber) (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Arabella (Richard Strauss) (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Autstiey and Fall der Stadt Mahagonny (Kurt Weill) (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Un Bailo in Maschesra (Verdi) (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - IiBarbiere de Siviglia (Gioacchino Rossini) (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Billy Budd (Benjamin Britten) (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Bitter Sweet (Norl Coward) (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Blossom Time (Franz Schubert) (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Le Boheme (Gioacchino Rossini) (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - The Bohemian Girl (Balfe) (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Bomarzo (Alberto Ginastzra) (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Boris Godunov (Modest Mussorgsky) (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Operas (C - .1)
    - La Campann Summersa (Ohorino Respighi) (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Carmen (Georges Bizet) (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Cavalleria Rusticana (Pietro Mascagni) (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Charodicika (Tchaikovsky) (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - The Chimes of Normandy (Robert Planquette) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - The Chocolate Soldier (Oscar Straus) (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Cinderella (Gioacchino Rossini) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Les Contes d'Hoffmann (Jacques Offenbuch) (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Le Coq d'Or (Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov) (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Cosi fan Tutte (Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart) (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Cyrano (Walter Damrosch) (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Dafni (Givsepps Mule) (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Death in Venice (Benjamin Britten) (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Doktor Faust (Ferruccio Busoni) (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Don Carlo (Verdi) (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Don Giovanni (Mozart) (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Don Pasqusle (Donize Hi) (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - The Duchers of Multi (Stephen Douglas Burton) (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - L'Ebrea (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Einstein on the Beach (Philip Glass) (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Elettra (Richard Strauss) (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - L'Elisir d'Amore (Donizetti) (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - The Emperor John (Louis Gruenberg) (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Ernani (Verdi) (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Escorial (Martin David Levy) (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Eugene Onegin (Tchaikovsky) (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Falstaff (Verdi) (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - La Fanciulla del West (Gioacchino Rossini) (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Faust (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Fidelio (Ludwig van Beethoven) (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - La File du Regiment (Gaetano Donizetti) (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - The Flaming Angel (Serge Prokotier) (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Die Fledermaus (John Strauss) (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Die Fliegende Hollander (Richard Wagner) (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Four Saints in Three Acts (Virgil Thomson) (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Francesca Da Rimini (Riccardo Zandonai) (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Die Fran Ohne Schatten (Richard Strauss) (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Der Freischutz (Carl Maria yen Weber) (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Goherdammerung (Richard Wagner) (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Good Morning Dearie (Jerome Kern) (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Goyescas (Enrigue Gandados) (Box 64, Folder 41)